the fuckers managed to get me i shouldn't be surprised though they get most everyone these
days through bribes hacking blackmail whatever works for them nothing is sacred anymore
should have been smarter more prepared maybe i wouldn't be in this mess and my family would
still be alive where'd you find the files i would have been a lottery
shock them ready reaching ain't got nothing to lose anymore so they won't be getting anything
from me at least i took some of them down which pissed them off more naturally
tell us how you acquired the files and we'll just kill you quickly
we just want to go home and be done with your lot you're just making it difficult on yourself
yeah baby you have to be quiet now everything's gonna be fine don't be afraid honey mama loves
you very much she knew it wouldn't be fine but she couldn't watch our baby so scared before the
end everyone else is collateral should have been smarter sent them someplace safe on time
oh no i knew this was a possibility but i always imagined i was capable enough to prevent it
i wanted to give my kid a normal life full of possibilities one that every child deserves
but here here we rarely get what is fair or what we want as it was trying to create
a better future this is what you get the people you do it for those you care most for
they die in a pool of their own blood scared and alone the innocent ones i'm so glad we
got to spend some quality time together you're pretty much useless but fret not jake we've
got all our files back and those you want to protect them from just ended already they buy
kill or cheat their way out if you say so and just sweep the ugly stuff under the rug
a year in this shithole not much to do here but think back on what happened
gotta keep myself busy while riding away nobody ever gets out anyway
okay the prison is getting more and more crowded each day more people come in most of them with
a story similar to mine guess this is it we're going on a little road trip asshole fuck
i just wish watching my cellmate take a dump wasn't the last thing i saw
take them to processing how was the dinner party last night for fuck's sake why haven't
they just killed me yet it was okay the kids were loud but hey they're kids glad it went
over well what is this place keep moving criminal how did you do this why do they have
my face huh hey it's the original i thought it'd be taller oh no what's next please jake
would you take a seat feeling comfortable what are you gonna do to me oh nothing much
just a bit of an upgrade now don't squirm too much this might sting a bit i heard what
happened to your family jake how sad but hey all's well that ends well huh now at least
we'll always know where you are and how to contact you amongst other things see
that wasn't so bad now was it what what's happening what did you do you should consider
yourself lucky jake the bcu2 unit is a wonderful piece of tech granted the process is usually
less personal each chip has to be individually set up according to the subject's age sex
constitution etc mistakes happen but you're what the directors consider a vip so we can't
afford any mistakes during your process plus i've been dying to get to know the famous
jake maddox the hero of the peep i was really looking forward to meeting you you know
i guess you could call it professional admiration i have to be honest i've been admiring your
work from afar i always considered your methods to be brutal but very effective out of all the
rebel factions you and your group seemed to have made most of an impact you were affected because
you knew the ends will always justify the means no matter the collateral you'd walk over
any number of corpses if it meant getting what you wanted and i respect that ah i rambled did
i ramble sorry about that anyway the setup should be completed soon so you'd be good to go
go where who are you people those things outside what is this place sorry jake i'm afraid i'm not
authorized to discuss that with you but the director specifically requested to see you before
you leave we shouldn't keep him waiting let me just adjust this and turn on the receiver and
that's it okay you can take him now try to be careful with him though the bcu2 is still
integrating into his central nervous system so he might not have full control of his bodily
functions why can i see clearly something feels wrong you really think i have to answer to that
just shut up and keep moving okay you can go in now he's ready hey if it isn't good old jake
how you doing jakey you even remember our last meeting it doesn't matter you want a drink you
oh come on immediately with the growling and the violence i thought you were more of a
methodical person judging by all the trouble you caused us well i'm going to have that
drink if you won't but you should because what's coming for you is going to make all
the shit you've been through look like a goddamn preschool play adaptation of shawshank
redemption i see the bcu2 has been installed maybe now the suits upstairs finally shut up
hope dr steward was nice enough to you she seemed really excited when she saw your name
in the ad the ad lance bring us a good candidate lance make sure the bcu2 is installed correctly
lance this lance that will hopefully now be the one to have the best eyes on the island
through you now if you behave nicely on the island and do me a favor here and there
i might how should i put this help you in a manner of speaking give you some well-earned
surprises but if you don't well then i might help someone else make your life there harder
you see where i'm getting at jakey i would if i had any fucking idea what you're talking about
ah so you have no clue whatsoever perfect well i'm not about to spoil the surprise the
viewers like a genuine reaction i think we're done here you can take them to the helipad
oh and please put on a good show you know for the people easy there with the straps
ah shut up well i guess i know what's coming next well it's been nice knowing you all for
a brief time but the time has come to say our goodbyes it's been the best of times it's been
the worst of times but whatever got you here you're here now you may have been experimented on
you may have been tortured a bit think of this as a new beginning a new clean slate
your endurance and survival skills will be tested and it's up to you to give it your
anything less might result in an instant death this is where we part ways but don't worry
we'll be watching you the world will be watching you good luck prisoners oh and the parachutes
open on the right what the hell kind of speech is that supposed to be drop them
secure communication with human asset established who's that greetings human asset
welcome to scum island tutorial protocol provided by the tech one corporation my designation is dual
energetic entity neural appliance sardina i am an artificial intelligence tasked with overseeing
the scum show protocols including the preparation of human assets secure channel closed hey there
are you new here i haven't seen you before no need to sneak like that yeah well i just got
blown out of a drop ship with nothing but a parachute i'd say caution is warranted fair enough
you must be exhausted come inside i think i could spare you a few supplies i'd appreciate
that detecting visual display malfunction in bcu2 unit designation 150474
reinitializing please stand by
reinitialization completed human asset may proceed so this is what it's gonna be like here huh
you might as well take these with me so human asset where are you going
i gotta find shelter and food other than that i can't see well dina wish me luck
i'm gonna need it